arcticfoxhaircolor.com 2019-11-05

# Privacy Policy – Arctic Fox - Dye For A Cause

Privacy Policy & Security  
  
This arcticfoxusa.com Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") governs your use of the arcticfoxusa.com website (the "Website"), which is owned by Boinca Inc. This policy does not cover the practices of companies that Boinca Inc. does not own or control, or the actions of people that Boinca Inc. does not employ or manage. Your privacy is important to us and we value your privacy so we have created this Privacy Policy to ensure that you understand our policies and procedures, what personal information we request if you wish to use certain portions of our Website and, ultimately, just how we use such personal information. This Privacy Policy is a part of and is incorporated into our Arcticfoxusa.com Terms of Use. For more information about the terms of use for this site, please visit our Terms of Use. By accessing or using our Website, you accept, without limitation or qualification, the terms of this Privacy Policy.  

Gathering Information  
  
Arcticfoxusa.com may request and collect personal information that you elect to provide to us ("Personal Information") when you (1) register with us, (2) participate in events, contests, or promotions, (3) send questions or comments to us, (4) purchase products. Personal Information we request may include; contact information such as name, address, phone number and email address, credit card (only upon purchasing our products) and sometimes ID verification information (upon contest winners) and information regarding how you became aware of the Arctic Fox hair dye. We do not participate in bulk email solicitations that you have not consented to receiving (i.e., "spam").  

Minors   
  
Our Website is not intended for users under the age of 18. Furthermore, we have no intention of collecting personally identifiable information from children under 18. You may visit our site, but you cannot make a purchase. You also cannot become a registered user, or use any service that asks for personal information. This policy is designed to protect children and us to take special steps to safeguard children's privacy.  

Cookies on arcticfoxusa.com  
  
Cookies enable arcticfoxusa.com to customize your user interface to speed up the process and facilitate your navigation through Arcticfoxusa.com website. We may use cookies to obtain non-personally identifiable information from website visitors. Such information may include your "Internet Protocol Address," operating system browser type and the referring website's address, if any ("non-Personal Information"). The cookies track your computer, not you. They are not connected to any personal information about you. Cookies are files your web browser places on your computer when you visit a website.   
  
Arcticfoxusa.com uses the Personal Information for the purposes indicated at the time you voluntarily provide such information and/or set forth in this Privacy Policy. The Personal Information that you provide will be available to arcticfoxusa.com, our agents, representatives and trusted service providers and contractors for limited purposes. These categories of use include, but may not be limited to, communicating to arcticfoxusa.com website visitors, offering certain products and services in connection with arcticfoxusa.com website. In addition, we may, from time to time, share your information with selected third parties in a variety of categories including, but not limited to, marketing, strategic partners and providers of similar products and services to provide you with opportunities to purchase products, programs or services that may be of interest to you.  
  
We will also disclose personal information if in our opinion such disclosure is required (i) by law, (ii) to protect and/or defend Arcticfoxusa.com' rights and/or (iii) to protect the personal safety of any individual. In addition, in the event that all or substantially all of arcticfoxusa.com' stock and/or assets are transferred or sold to another entity, arcticfoxusa.com may transfer personal information to the acquiring entity.  
  
We may amend our Privacy Policy & Security at any time, by posting such revised Privacy Policy & Security on this page, you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. We invite you to check back periodically to see if we have made any changes.
